[
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            3
        ],
        "question": "What is the purpose of using a popularity-based system for new customers in this recommendation system design?",
         "answer": "Popularity-based system targets new customers with the most popular products sold on a business's website and is very useful to cold start a recommendation engine.",
        "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Collaborative Filtering"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            5
        ],
        "question": "What does  `truncatedSVD` perform?",
         "answer": "It is used for performing the principal component analysis in this recommendation system.",
        "task": "Principal Component Analysis",
        "skill": "SVD"
    },
      {
        "cell_ids": [
            7
        ],
          "question": "What are the dimensions of the matrix resulting from `pivot_table` function?",
          "answer": "The shape is 706 rows × 810 columns",
        "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
        "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            8
        ],
        "question": "What is the main idea behind using matrix factorization in this recommendation system?",
         "answer": "To  determine some underlying mathematical structure in the user rating matrix, which can help us predict missing ratings in the future.",
        "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
    },
  {
        "cell_ids": [
            13
        ],
         "question": "How does the notebook identify the movie for the corresponding movie id in the recommendation section?",
        "answer": "It uses the `movies` dataframe and looks for a match with  `movieId` column, then gets corresponding movie title.",
         "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
        "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
     {
         "cell_ids": [
            16
         ],
        "question": "What type of data is used for the third recommendation system?",
          "answer":"The recommendation system uses the product descriptions",
         "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
        "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            16
        ],
        "question": "What method is used for extracting numerical features from the text of the product description?",
         "answer": "TfidfVectorizer",
          "task": "Topic Modeling",
        "skill": "Latent Dirichlet Allocation"
    },
   {
        "cell_ids": [
            22
        ],
        "question": "What is the function of KMeans algorithm?",
        "answer":"To group similar product description in to one group.",
          "task": "Customer Segmentation",
         "skill":"K-means Clustering"
    },
   {
        "cell_ids": [
           27
        ],
        "question": "What is the main idea of  Item-Item based recommendation system, in contrast to User-Based collaborative model?",
        "answer": "Item-to-item collaborative filtering matches each of the user’s purchased and rated items to similar items, then combines those similar items into a recommendation list while user-based CF matches the user to similar customers",
         "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Collaborative Filtering"
    },
    {
          "cell_ids": [
            29
        ],
       "question": "What does the output of the `recommend` function shows?",
         "answer": "It outputs the top words in each product cluster based on product descriptions.",
         "task": "Topic Modeling",
        "skill": "Latent Dirichlet Allocation"
    }
]